{
  "level": 2,
  "unit": 6,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "I write with a _____________ .", "answer": "pencil" },
        { "prompt": "The _____________ sticks to metal.", "answer": "magnet" },
        {
          "prompt": "The company will _____________ the magazine.",
          "answer": "publish"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "What will we eat for _____________ tonight?",
          "answer": "supper"
        },
        { "prompt": "I wrote a _____________ to Grandma.", "answer": "letter" },
        { "prompt": "My teacher is a nice _____________ .", "answer": "lady" },
        {
          "prompt": "I like to eat _____________ on my mashed potatoes.",
          "answer": "gravy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The man made a _____________ trip around the world.",
          "answer": "solo"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Will you hold the door _____________ for me?",
          "answer": "open"
        },
        { "prompt": "Do you smell that _____________ ?", "answer": "odor" },
        {
          "prompt": "The old pipes are made of _____________ .",
          "answer": "lead"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Do not _____________ the paintings in the museum.",
          "answer": "touch"
        },
        { "prompt": "The shop _____________ is locked.", "answer": "door" },
        {
          "prompt": "I spilled milk down the _____________ of my shirt.",
          "answer": "front"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ needs to pick up this litter!",
          "answer": "Someone"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Kris lives in the _____________ of Maine.",
          "answer": "state"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We need to _____________ the broken lamp.",
          "answer": "replace"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When will she be _____________ years old?",
          "answer": "nine"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Sue lives _____________ miles from her grandfather.",
          "answer": "ninety"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Stay on this _____________ of the fence.",
          "answer": "side"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Kevin rides his bike on the _____________.",
          "answer": "sidewalk"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The girl washes her _____________ each morning.",
          "answer": "face"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "You will need a raincoat if you are going _____________ .",
          "answer": "outside"
        },
        { "prompt": "Look at _____________ new toys!", "answer": "these" },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ swims in the pond.",
          "answer": "tadpole"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I will write a _____________ to my cousin.",
          "answer": "letter"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Can the _____________ lift this paper clip?",
          "answer": "magnet"
        },
        { "prompt": "Do you like to sit _____________ ?", "answer": "alone" },
        {
          "prompt": "The tree is _____________ the house.",
          "answer": "beside"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Three children sit at the _____________ table.",
          "answer": "round"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "The campers _____________ a fire to stay warm.",
          "answer": "lit"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We saw a _____________ mouse in the yard.",
          "answer": "little"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Jay bought a new _____________ of paints.",
          "answer": "set"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The pieces of gold will _____________ at the bottom of the river.",
          "answer": "settle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Please _____________ that paper into small pieces.",
          "answer": "rip"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Throw a stone to make the water _____________ .",
          "answer": "ripple"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Dan wrote the shopping list on a _____________ of paper.",
          "answer": "pad"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you know how to _____________ a boat?",
          "answer": "paddke"
        },
        { "prompt": "Val sat in the _____________ seat.", "answer": "middle" },
        { "prompt": "I blew a huge soap _____________ !", "answer": "bubble" },
        {
          "prompt": "Is it warm enough to play _____________ ?",
          "answer": "outside"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Mom will _____________ my old shoes with new ones.",
          "answer": "replace"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Kim’s dog likes to _____________ her everywhere.",
          "answer": "follow"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I _____________ to music on the radio.",
          "answer": "listen"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Can you make me _____________ to eat?",
          "answer": "something"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Do you know the _____________ to the school?",
          "answer": "way"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The bird flew _____________ from its nest.",
          "answer": "away"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Don’t dig up the _____________ of the plant.",
          "answer": "root"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I buy a _____________ at the parade.",
          "answer": "balloon"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We like to _____________ hide-and-seek in the park.",
          "answer": "play"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Our teacher will _____________ our artwork.",
          "answer": "display"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Can you _____________ the book on the top shelf?",
          "answer": "reach"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I _____________ swimming at the beach.",
          "answer": "enjoy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Can you _____________ how to play the game?",
          "answer": "explain"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The cows are in the _____________ eating grass.",
          "answer": "meadow"
        },
        { "prompt": "Look at the _____________ rabbit!", "answer": "little" },
        {
          "prompt": "The table is in the _____________ of the room.",
          "answer": "middle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Will you help me _____________ this puzzle?",
          "answer": "complete"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Is this _____________ money to buy the toy?",
          "answer": "enough"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The family paddles a canoe on the _____________ .",
          "answer": "river"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Meg wore a purple _____________ to school.",
          "answer": "jumper"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I can see _____________ when I stand on my toes.",
          "answer": "higher"
        },
        { "prompt": "Look at that _____________ twinkle!", "answer": "star" },
        {
          "prompt": "The night sky is clear and _____________ .",
          "answer": "starry"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Marco planted tomatoes in the _____________ .",
          "answer": "garden"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "It is _____________ to write in pencil than in pen.",
          "answer": "better"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We had chicken soup for _____________ .",
          "answer": "dinner"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I see my _____________ each year for a checkup.",
          "answer": "doctor"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Buy some cheese at the _____________ .",
          "answer": "market"
        },
        { "prompt": "What a _____________ dog!", "answer": "hairy" },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you _____________ playing games with your friends?",
          "answer": "enjoy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The pet store had a _____________ of cat toys in the window.",
          "answer": "display"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Our school day ends in the _____________ .",
          "answer": "afternoon"
        },
        { "prompt": "Has _____________ seen my backpack?", "answer": "anyone" },
        {
          "prompt": "Lee ate _____________ on his plate.",
          "answer": "everything"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
